順便說一下，別忘了帶手電筒。森林裏晚上會非常黑。
By the way, don't forget to bring a flashlight. It gets really dark in the forest at night.
明白了。那驅蟲劑呢？有很多蟲子嗎？
Got it. What about bug spray? Are there a lot of insects?
是的，最好帶上一些。可能會有蚊子和其他蟲子。
Yeah, it's better to have some. There might be mosquitoes and other bugs.
好的，我會帶上。那裏有手機信號嗎？
Okay, I'll pack it. Will we have cell phone signal there?
信號可能很弱。所以這是一個遠離科技的好機會。
The signal might be weak. So it's a good chance to disconnect from technology.
沒錯。我很期待晚上看星星。
That's true. I'm excited to stargaze at night.
我也是。那裏的天空非常清澈。我們可以看到很多星座。
Me too. The sky there is really clear. We can see a lot of constellations.
聽起來很棒。我們應該帶相機去捕捉美好瞬間嗎？
Sounds amazing. Should we bring a camera to capture the beautiful moments?
當然。如果不記錄下這麽棒的經歷就太可惜了。
Definitely. It would be a pity not to record such a great experience.
好的，我一定會帶上。期待我們的露營之旅！
Alright, I'll make sure to bring it. Looking forward to our camping trip!